{
    "id": "af237aaa73484d36b2737034e655191b",
    "title": "Though and although – grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "00412f07a4f8470ca2db503a647cbabe",
            "title": "Though And Although",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "....................................... my grandmother is very old, she can still read without glasses.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even if",
                        "However",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... he was very tired, he completed the work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Although",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "......................................... the policemen ran fast, they couldn’t catch the thief.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Even if",
                        "As though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................. they gave him the best medical care, they could not save his life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "However",
                        "Though",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... he left home early, he arrived late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "Though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ she had the required qualifications, she did not get the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As though",
                        "Even if",
                        "Although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... they are rich, they lead simple lives.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Although",
                        "As though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ she was ill, she went to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................. our team played well, they could not win the championship.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... my grandmother can’t read or write, she is wiser than most people.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Even if",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}